What an unbelievably crazy week on kick.
I was just talking about the French streamer Jean Parmanov who passed away in his
leap on stream after a marathon of abuse from some other streamers.
And just now I literally just finished streaming Resident Evil 6
and I was taking a little tinkle and I got sent a little something that is so
diabolical. I had the hop back in the saddle and yap about it. It is
incomprehensible that yet another potential death was just streamed on kick.
I'm recording this an hour after it happened and the victim is currently still in the ICU.
So I guess by the time I post this I'll know whether or not they passed away.
But I'm going to keep this part in here right now because it's up in the air.
A kick streamer, Roger Jackson who was the son of rampage Jackson and also a professional fighter
just went fucking ballistic on a wrestler during a wrestling event on stream.
He picks the wrestler up, slams him on the mat and then lays down 27 punches to the man's skull.
Most of which were delivered while he was unconscious.
And by the end of it he is bleeding and bloodied. They couldn't wake him up.
They said he was barely breathing and someone even used the word flatline that he was flat
line in the ring. This is not fake. This is not scripted.
I did my best to censor this. It is brutal. It is extremely hard to watch.
I also cut the clip short but they pan back and he is covered in blood.
Roger Jackson is a professional fighter who has unloaded I counted 27 blows to an unconscious man.
And they all are connecting. This is not like fake. It's not like he's pulling any of his punches.
They are all hitting squarely on this man's skull. Bouncing his head off of the mat.
And I said most of them were when he was unconscious. All of them are while he's unconscious.
When I watch the back it's clear that when he slammed him on the mat his head hit the mat and it
knocked him out immediately. So all 27 potentially more punches that he threw were on an unconscious man.
That can be fatal. That is most often times fatal. And he wasn't done either. It's not like he
just stopped and said okay well that's plenty. I've had my fill. He was still going. The only
reason there weren't more punches thrown by him is because the other wrestlers were able to separate
him. But he was fighting against them to go back and keep beating this unconscious man.
He probably wouldn't have stopped punching him until his head popped like a balloon.
It's extremely scary and even if he does pull through this could have life changing repercussions
with brain damage and so many other complications for the rest of his life if he even survives which
we don't know yet. He apparently flatlined in the ring and is currently still in the ICU and we
don't have any updates. This is terrifying stuff. Hello it's Charles first thing in the morning
here and we don't have a ton of official updates on the condition of that wrestler. But the father
of Roger Jackson, Rampage Jackson gave an update where he is saying that psycho stew that's named
the wrestler is alive and is stable and he also says that he's clearing up misinformation about
his son. But then in his statement he doesn't clear up any misinformation. He just confirms what
everyone already knows that this was completely out of control in excusable behavior that Rampage Jackson
also doesn't condone. So I don't know what misinformation he thinks he's clearing up with this.
He's just agreeing with what everyone else is saying that his son went fucking berserk. I guess
maybe the misinformation demon that he was exercising here was about his son actually getting
like the permission for payback on psycho stew for an earlier confrontation. And what he's referring
to there is they had like a little beef before the event started and someone had told Roger Jackson
that he could like double leg take down psycho stew in the ring and then throw like a fake punch
in that would be it to like settle the beef and create like this storyline. But
Roger Jackson on stream on camera says that he is going to hurt psycho stew. He said he will not
stop punching him until people will yank him off of him. So he took that like pseudo invite like
green light to be involved in the wrestling event as a permission slip to go brutally assault this
man and beat him within an inch of his life. Like I think you could also make a case that this
is attempted murder. This was premeditated assault that he planned on not stopping at any point
until third party's intervened. Like I really think you could make like a real argument that he
had went in there with the full intentions of killing psycho stew. That's what it looks like to me.
That's indefensible. You can see him literally planning it off the back of them giving him like
the instructions for a work where he'd come in and he'd deliver like a hit like a fake hit and then
he'd be pulled off and that'd be the end of it. And he is saying but watch this I'm going to keep
punching him. Like he is blatantly stating this. It is very clearly a premeditated assault.
And like I said I really think his goal was to kill psycho stew there. It really seems like
that was his mission. And you can't chalk this up to confusion where he was directed to do something
but then just went a little far like mistakenly. He is with his own voice, his own vocal folds
flapping with with their own volition here. He is stating they told me to do this but instead
I'm going to do this. I'm going to punch him as many times as I possibly can. He is stating
clearly that they told him one thing and he is not doing that. Instead he is going to punch the
shit out of him, beat him within an inch of his life. You can't possibly say that he just got
confused with the the stage directions here of the storyline. He is saying that he is going to go
punch him as many times as possible and disregard what they said he is permitted to do. Like what they
planned on. It is premeditated assault by every possible definition. Now let's start at all of this
and I've seen people joking about it like oh ha ha, Roger Jackson must not know that wrestling is
fake and he thought the heel was being mean to his favorite baby face suit took matters into his
own hands. But what actually happened is Roger Jackson was touring the event and meeting the
wrestlers backstage. And of course the wrestlers are all playing characters and when it comes to
wrestling there is a little something called kayfabe and so they are going to portray their
character to the best of their ability and keep everything as authentic and genuine as possible.
And Psycho Stew was in character and misunderstood that Roger Jackson was not a worker in the event.
What about here? Psycho Stew. Psycho Stew. What you don't know me? Hell no.
He's not a fucking worker bro. Yeah what the fuck was that?
What the fuck was that? You all sell it?
Dude he's not a fucking worker bro. What the fuck was that?
Oh no. I don't know. I'll fuck him up. I know I know you will.
And he takes it way too far when he takes a beer can. I don't know if it's like a real beer
can or like one of those breakaway like stunt ones but he takes it and he crushes it on
Roger Jackson's head. Then you can see him get really fired up about it and all the other
wrestlers are also saying to Psycho Stew like bro what the fuck are you doing? He's not like a
worker here or anything that was too far and that's what started this and then Roger Jackson
waited until their match. Then he stormed in and then beat him potentially to death for it.
Now I think if Roger Jackson had swung on Psycho Stew after the beer can thing you could definitely
make a strong case that it was acting in self-defense because that is unexpected. It was unprovoked
and it was kind of a crazy thing for Psycho Stew to do not knowing for sure if Roger Jackson was
a worker in the event or not. It was a bad judgment call for sure from Stew. And he was just like
way too fucking committed to being the heel. Like he was really deep into his method acting like
fucking shy a love style and he did the beer can thing and it was definitely over the line.
But here's something a lot of people aren't showing enough of that Psycho Stew was very apologetic
when he learned that Roger Jackson was not a worker at the event. He apologized three times. They
shook hands multiple times and Roger said like hey it's good I get it. Multiple times meanwhile
he was just like bubbling with anger waiting for his chance to fucking assault this man.
I know you keep thinking we're working. We're always working. We're always working. I get it now.
Now you know what I'm saying. We're always working. What a fucking worm. This is some slimy behavior
here. This is some turbo ass. Roger Jackson is now pretending that he understands and forgives
Psycho Stew who is very apologetic mind you and he's explaining like look I saw the cameras. I
thought that this was like another work that we were building a storyline. This is that and
where Roger Jackson is like no no I get it and he's like shaking his hand and everything.
Meanwhile he is actively planning of assaulting this man beating him unconscious and fucking
leaving him eating meals through a straw as he is like pretending to let bygones be bygones here
and that they're on good terms as fucking unhinged. Now before showing you some more of the aftermath
here let me introduce you to Psycho Stew. I think you should get a little bit of the lore behind this
wrestler that Roger Jackson beat so severely hospitalizing in the ICU and apparently caused
a flatline in the ring. Pro in 2009 I had just got out of the military probably about six months
earlier. I got out of the military I joined Knox Pro you know because I needed something to focus
on. I needed something to help me adjust back in the civilian life. You know a lot of veterans
it's hard for them to readjust in this civilian life coming from the life of the military.
I'm an American soldier that suffers from PTSD. Being in front of a crowd it doesn't give me as much
anxiety and aggression as I thought it would. Yeah Psycho Stew is a veteran who was suffering from PTSD
and found wrestling as a means of escapism and fell in love with the sport and now is currently
hospitalized in the ICU but apparently a stable so hopefully rampage Jackson is accurate with
that claim that he is alive and stable. That would be wonderful news but what an unbelievable set of
circumstances that led to his hospitalization here. Yes he made a mistake with rampage Jackson's
son here not knowing whether or not he was a worker and still building the storyline anyway under
the impression he was but it's not a mistake that should have led to something like this especially
when he did everything in his power to try and rectify it and try and apologize for his mistake
and explain why it happened and ensure that it was totally unintentional and there wasn't meant to be
any bad blood or anything and he thought that he did accomplish that but clearly Raja Jackson didn't
actually think so he was just acting. Raja Jackson was flexing his thespian skills here when he was
pretending that everything was okay between those two because what he was actually doing was
plotting a premeditated assault on psychoste. Again that potential argument of self-defense that
has poofed away like Timmy Turner's fairy godparents that ship sailed a long time ago because he didn't
act in response to the threat like after the beer can was crushed on his head which again he
wasn't expecting and that can be dangerous but he didn't like act in the heat of the moment to
defend himself from that or anything instead he let it marinate let his rage bubble up and then
waited for his opportunity to get revenge later. There is no longer a possible case of self-defense
here like yes he was wronged but he didn't like trying to defend himself from that threat or anything
he pretended to like move on from it with the guy who did it and then waited to attack him later
and I think you can make a very strong case that it was attempted murder at the very least it is a
premeditated assault and based on the things he was saying leading up to it and based on the behavior
in the ring when he was delivering 27-ish blows to an unconscious man's skull I really think there
is a strong argument to be made that he was in there doing that solely to try and kill him.
All of this on-stream mind you and you can even see him respond to the news that the guy that he
just unloaded 27 punches on in the ring while he was unconscious is potentially flatlined.
Hello
Hey where are you at?
I just wanted to double that I got my fuckery start rolling over to solve the video.
It should piss me off though Andre.
I understand that but now they can't wake the nigga up.
He's fucking in the ring, fucking flat.
I'm bad.
I'm taking care of this.
I'll call you back later.
This guy does not seem to care at all.
This is a fucking monster right here.
In response to hearing that the guy flatlined he just says, my bad.
It's crazy.
Crados had more empathy for the people that he killed in very similar fashion by the way with
like the unbelievable amount of blows to the head but at least in Crado's case the people he was
fighting they were at least conscious. All of these were delivered to an unconscious man.
A man who never even saw this coming by the way because he storms into the ring grabs him and
then slams him. So it wasn't even a fight but he walks away feeling so fucking tough and
accomplished about it with no remorse at all for potentially killing this man.
Todd I'm not fucking playing with me bro.
Real shit.
One of them was basing fucking bimmy.
Todd I everybody fucking play with me and shit.
I'm always playing and shit.
Call me bits and shit.
Not no fucking bits bro.
At the end of the day I'm gonna stand up for my fucking self because I'm tired everybody
fucking play with me bro.
Real shit.
He's walking away from this with his chin held high.
Extremely proud of what's unfolded here.
It seems like this might be the happiest moment of his life.
The way that he is perceiving this is him standing up for himself.
He is not able to have a grasp on the severity of what just happened here.
He thinks that because the disrespect that he encountered early in the day he was entirely
justified to potentially murder this man.
And by the way the wrestlers that were calling him a bitch.
Well I imagine they were saying that because he basically sucker punched this guy
potentially to death.
The guy never even had a chance to fight back because he came into the ring when his back was
turned slammed them down immediately knocking him unconscious.
It wasn't even a fight it was a surprise attack.
So I imagine that's what he's referencing when it comes to the wrestlers like insulting him
and the one that bit him with everyone that was like getting on top of Raja to get him away
from psycho stew on the ground because he was still going back to try and make sure he was dead it
seems.
Now on the rest of the clip here one of the wrestlers from the event starts walking towards them talking
to them trying to get them to stay probably until police get there would be my guest.
But he is talking to them and he is shit talking trying to go to him into staying
and he's like talking about like I'll fight you right now and then it's a back and forth.
But Raja Jackson reiterates that he wants to fight more of them there.
He wants to continue to beat people within an inch of their life there.
It's scary.
I cannot imagine a world where he does not go to jail for this.
I really can't.
Rampage Jackson has tons and tons of money sure.
But I don't know if he's going to be able to outspend the attempted murder charges that
his son just racked up here.
Now of course I'm not a lawyer and I don't have like a magic crystal ball that I can ponder the
orb of to see the future but my guess would be that there will be attempted murder charges
for this incident.
Because I mean I really think it's like it feels like that's what the goal here was
when Raja Jackson was delivering these blows.
I mean I think at bare minimum you're getting some serious assault charges.
Like no matter what I think he should be thrown in the slamer for this.
This behavior is completely unacceptable.
He knew exactly what he was doing.
He even on stream states what he's about to do and he clearly doesn't stop until he is pulled
off and then still wants to keep going.
All of these blows delivered to an unconscious man.
How could you possibly say this is anything other than him trying to kill him?
It's it's fucking sickening.
Now like I said it to the start of the video I've recorded all of this pretty much immediately after
it happened.
So we still don't know how psycho stew is doing if he's going to pull through from all of this
or not.
But by the time I post this video I imagine we'll have some kind of update so I'll go ahead and put
that at the beginning of the video but as of right now fingers crossed that he pulls through.
Like yeah he definitely did make a big mistake with the beer can thing but I don't think it's
something that should have cost him his life here in this manner.
This shit is unhinged.
Anyway that's really about it.
See ya.